Charles R. Martin Photographs, 1945-2011 AIS.2012.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, 1945-1998; II.
  - 35mm Negatives, 1.
    - 1980
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment; Tony Haberstock; United Way; Kmart; Steve Snyder; Dave Gebhart; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Salvation Army; and the Elks Lodge. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Test, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 48)
      - Personal- Copies, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 49)
      - Personal, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 50-51)
      - Personal- OM-1 Test, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 52-53)
      - United Way- Louise Child Care Center, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 54-55)
      - Personal- Steelers- Houston- 1980 AFC Championship (Box 51, Folder 56)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 57-59)
      - Personal- Tony Haberstrok Passports, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 60)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 61-64)
      - Personal- Leica III w/ Summar, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 65)
      - B.F. Interiors & Sweetwater Class, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Elks, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 2-4)
      - Dave Gebhart, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Personal- OM-1, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Steve Snyder- Candidate - DDS, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 7-9)
      - Personal- Ocracoke – Easter '80, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 12-16, 62-65)
      - Personal- Sewickley, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Personal, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten & Yves Alarie Canadian Passport, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Berger- Slide Copy, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Kmart, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Salvation Army, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 22-25)
      - United Way, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 26-34, 36-43, 58, 60-61)
      - 5.A. & Misc., 1980 (Box 52, Folder 35)
      - Personal- Allentown Bike Race, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 44, 47, 49)
      - United Way- Boys Club, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 45-46)
      - Personal- Auction, Dog Walking, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 48)
      - Somerville Bike Races, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 50, 54-55, 59)
      - Thursday Night Bike Races, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 51)
      - M-3 Test, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 52)
      - United Way & Thursday Night Bike Races, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 53)
      - Personal- Thursday Races, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 56)
      - Allentown Race, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 57)
      - Kmart- Cranberry, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 1, 14, 37)
      - Kmart- Aliquippa, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 2, 22-23, 38)
      - Passports- Allan T. Dias & Wife, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Personal- Test, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Kmart- Vandergrift, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 5, 47)
      - United Way- J.T. Thomas & Mr. Rose, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - United Way- Maurice Anderson, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Dynamic Equip Corporation, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 8, 36, 44)
      - Bette Roth, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - United Way, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Delores Hadley- Copy Work, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - TRBC- Bike Race Banners in Bellevue, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Personal- Bike Races – Thursday Nights, early August, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Kmart- Leechburg, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 15-16)
      - Bike Race, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 17, 19-21)
      - Bike Race- Winners, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Sweetwater Festival & St. Barnabas, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 24-25)
      - Sweetwater Festival, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 26-28)
      - St. Barnabas Festival, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - United Way- Team, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 30-34)
      - Kmart- Aliquippa and Cranberry, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 35)
      - Personal- Tom – Passports, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 39)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation- Roy Marburger, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 40)
      - N. J., 1980 (Box 53, Folder 41-43)
      - Kmart- Cranberry- Conveyers, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 45)
      - Kmart, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 46)
      - Pirates, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 48-56, 58-60)
      - Empty Sleeves- 8012.2-8012.3 (Pirates), 1980 (Box 53, Folder 57)
      - Red Cross, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 61-71)
    - 1981
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment; Red Cross; Kmart; Hugh Stubs Co.; United Way; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Three River Arts Festival; Salvation Army; Vocational Rehabilitation Center. Also included are Martin's personal photographs, passport photos taken for friends, and camera test photos.
      - 3 Rivers Arts- Tom, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
      - 3 Rivers Arts, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Preston Passports, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Personal- Hugh Stubb's Trip, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Personal, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 6-10, 12, 14)
      - Personal- SwissAir Plane, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Personal- Plane, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - United Way, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 15-18, 52-54)
      - Sweetwater- "Swing Ding", 1981 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - Dynamic Equipment & Marianne Felterer Passports, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - Ken Bell- PR Picture, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 22-25, 28, 30-31)
      - Kmart- Leechburg, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 26, 38, 50)
      - Kmart- Leechburg & Westview, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 27)
      - M-3- Plattsburgh, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      - Ms. W. A. Tanskey Passports, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      - Minolta Test, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 34)
      - Elks Lodge, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Leica III, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 36)
      - Leica IIIa- Summar, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 37)
      - Lens Comparison Test, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 39)
      - Personal- Passport Pic-Kitty, John Hadley, Phil Duncan, Ginny Duncan, Ms. Alarie, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 40)
      - Kmart, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 41)
      - Kmart & Personal, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 42)
      - Joyce Williams- PR Pics, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      - 135 mm Hektor Test IIIa, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 44)
      - Spence- Passports, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 45)
      - Ocracoke- Edgar Howard, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 46)
      - Ocracoke, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 47)
      - Personal- Income Tax Copies & Ocracoke, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 48)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 49)
      - Hugh Stubbs Co., 1981 (Box 54, Folder 51)
      - Blevins Passports, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 55)
      - Salvation Army, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 56-58)
      - Test, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 59)
      - Easter Seals & Dynamic Equipment, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 60)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - AGFA Test, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Kmart- Leechburg Opening, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Kmart- West View, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Photo Color Test, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - St. Barnabas, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - United Way, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 7-12)
      - Personal- McConnells Mills, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Tom M, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 15-16, 18-32, 35-37)
      - Kitty's Shots Cabaret Crew, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Personal- Sewickley Street Scenes, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 33)
      - Personal- Pittsburgh Street Scenes, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 34)
      - 3 River Arts Festival, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 38)
      - XP1 Test, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 39-40)
      - XP1 vs. Tri X Test, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 41)
      - Kmart- Pittsburgh (West View), 1981 (Box 55, Folder 42)
      - Personal- Bike Ride, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 43)
      - Duncan & Jaguese- Copy, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 44)
      - Ocracoke, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 45-46, 52-53)
      - Kitty- Pelicans, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 47)
      - Alarie Children- Passports & Barn Shots, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 58)
      - Alarie Passports, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 49)
      - Berger- New S.S.U., 1981 (Box 55, Folder 50)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 51)
      - Kmart- McCandless- Store # 3577, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 54)
      - Kmart- West View, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 55)
      - Kmart- Washington, PA, Store # 4009, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 56)
      - Kmart- Pittsburgh (West View)- Store #3529, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 57)
      - United Way- Spec. Team, Hill House, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 58-60)
      - United Way- Spec. Team, Hill House, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Kmart- Washington, Pa., #4009, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 3-4)
      - United Way- Nick Stepauovich- Iron Workers Union, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - United Way, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 6, 8)
      - Personal, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 7, 9, 11-12)
      - Berger Instruments, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Joe White – Dawes, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 13-15)
      - Kmart- Mt. Pleasant Store # 9770, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Kmart- West View, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 17-20)
      - Kmart- McCandless, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Kitty & Cynthia Mitchel P.R. Pix, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 22-23)
      - Mary Rylko, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 24-27)
      - Rehearsal Dinner & North Park Misc., 1981 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - Trees, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - Personal & Dawes, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - 1982
      Subjects include Ocracoke Island, North Carolina; Kmart; Hot Harry's Club; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Dynamic Equipment; Vocational Rehabilitation Center; Salvation Army; Pittsburgh Blind Association; United Way; St. Barnabas; Kit Modeling; Sweetwater; Newark Ohio Art Show. Also included are Martin's personal photographs, passport photographs of friends and family, and camera test images.
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 31, 40-41, 56)
      - Kmart, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - United Way- Awards, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 33, 36)
      - United Way Awards & Alcoa, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 34)
      - United Way Awards & Pittsburgh Child Guidance Center, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 35)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 37-39)
      - Berger Slide Copies, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 42)
      - Copy of VT Instrument, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 43)
      - Personal- Store Windows- Mannequins, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 44)
      - Kit, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 45, 55)
      - Newark Ohio & Kits Show Opening, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 46, 61)
      - Vocational Rehabalitation Center- Meeting, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 47-48)
      - St. Barnabus- Birthday Party, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 49)
      - Mr. Meola & Misc. Snow Pix, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 50)
      - Kmart- Washington, PA & Mt. Pleasant, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 51)
      - Kmart- McCandless, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 52)
      - United Way- CFC Awards, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 53-54)
      - Pennsylvania Blind Association- Meeting, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 57-58)
      - Kmart-Mt. Pleasant, Fixture Day, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 59)
      - Salvation Army- Meeting, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 60)
      - Salvation Army- Meeting, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
      - Sewickley YMCA- Swim Team 1981-82 Season, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Kmart- Wexford Store #3577, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - United Way- Steeler Luncheon, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 6-8)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- 1982 Graduation (Box 57, Folder 9, 12, 14, 16-18)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation- Alpha Bldg. – Administration Offices, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 11, 13)
      - United Way- Awards, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Personal- Mamiya U Test, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 19-21, 57)
      - Kmart- Mt. Pleasant- Opening Day, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Berger Slide Copies, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 23, 30)
      - Personal- Kitty, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - Hot Harry's Club- July 4th Cranberry Park 10K, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - Kmart- Wexford, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - Sal, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      - Personal- 2nd Mamiya U Test, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 28)
      - Personal- Triathlon, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 29)
      - Personal- Duncan & Jaguese- Shooting, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 31)
      - Personal, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 32)
      - Personal- Joligor Test, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 33)
      - Mamiya U Test, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 34)
      - Soliger Test & Slide Copies, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 35)
      - Ocracoke Cabaret, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 36)
      - Ocracoke-Kit- Catalog pictures, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 37)
      - Kits Catalog Picture- Ocracoke, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 38)
      - Personal- Thursday Night Races & Shenango Triathlon Start, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 39)
      - Shenango Triathlon & Kmart, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 40)
      - Toy Catalog – Ocracoke, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 41)
      - Kmart –Wexford & Mac and Self on Eve. Mag. TV, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 42)
      - Kmart- Mt. Pleasant, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 43)
      - United Way- Westinghouse Meeting, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 44-47)
      - United Way- Report Meeting – Katy's Park, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 48-52)
      - Sweetwater P.R., 1982 (Box 57, Folder 53-54)
      - Dale Newman, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 55)
      - North American Bike Trip w/ Joe Bullick & Pittsburgh eve. Bldgs., 1982 (Box 57, Folder 56)
      - M-3 Summicron vs. Canon Test, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 58)
    - 1983
      Subjects include United Way; Special Olympics; Vocational Rehabilitation Center; Dynamic Equipment; Pittsburgh Triathlon. Also included are Martin's personal photographs, passoport photos of friends and family, and camera test photos.
      - Fred Mitchelli & Bames Mills (?), 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Kmart- Washington, PA, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Kmart- Warren Store # 428, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Kmart- Oil City PA.- Store # 378 Closing, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 5-6, 16)
      - Sutter Passports, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center- Mulads Award – To Ginny Thornburgh, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center- Mark Malone, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 9-11)
      - United Way- CFC- Rocky Bleier, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 12-13)
      - Mac Suter - Passports, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Remnar Passports, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Kitty, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 18-19)
      - Personal- Ron Walsher 50th Birthday Party & Joe Whites Arboretum, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Personal- M4-2 Test & 35mm Canon, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Personal- M4-2 Test, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Garry Smith D.C.- AD Shots, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 23-24)
      - Personal- Sweetwater Class, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - Personal- Camera Test, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Kitty and Gary, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - United Way, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 28-29, 46-57, 59-62)
      - Personal, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 30-33)
      - Personal- Summieron Test, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - United Way- Meeting- Union Officials at Press Club, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - Personal- Mamiya- Ocracoke, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 36)
      - Personal- New Summieron Test- M4-2, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 37)
      - United Way- Case Histories, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 38-39, 43)
      - Gary Smith D. C., 1983 (Box 58, Folder 40-41)
      - Misc.- M-4, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 42)
      - M-2- Camera Test, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 44)
      - Special Olympics- Penn Hills- Mamiya Universal, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 45)
      - United Way- Hill House, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 58)
      - United Way- Vocational Rehab Center- Handicap Counseling/ F&CS- group therapy, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 63)
      - United Way- F&CS Stress Counseling, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 64-65)
      - Gary and Kit's Wedding, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1-8)
      - Gary and Kitty's Wedding- Wedding Preparations, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - United Way- Market Square R- Leica, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - United Way- Market Square R, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 11-12)
      - Personal- Pittsburgh Triathlon, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Pittsburgh Triathlon, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Kitty's & Cynthia's Play, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center- PR Pix of L. Wildman, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Personal- Bam, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - United Way- Sp. Team, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 18-21)
      - Personal- Pittsburgh Point at Dusk, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Personal- Tom in 8ft pond- Quad, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center- Monessen, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 24-27)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 28, 48)
      - Kitty - Cynthia- Children's Play, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - Kitty- M-70, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - Gatan, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 31-32)
      - Pond, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - Passports, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 34)
      - Bio-Energetics, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 35-36)
      - Personal- Misc., 1983 (Box 59, Folder 37)
      - United Way- Meadows, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 38-42)
      - Hot Harrys Party- 60th Birthday, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 43)
      - Marathon Bus, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 44)
      - Personal- Mamiya Universal, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 45-46)
      - McConnells Mills, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 47)
      - Copies for Ann Jenkins- 1847 Newspapers stuck on furniture, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 49)
      - Quality Inn – Warrendale Architect Shots, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 50)
      - Canon III w/ Summar #423106, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 51)
      - Personal- Camera Test, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 52)
    - 1984
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment; Hot Harry's Runners; Vocational Rehabilitation Center; United Way; Bio-Energetiks; Golden Quill Awards. Also included are Martin's personal photos and camera test photos.
      - Personal- Semester at Sea, Universe Ship, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 53)
      - Personal- Semester at Sea– Universe Ship, Nature Shots, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 54)
      - Personal- Nature Shots, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 55)
      - Personal- Nature and Wildlife images- Universe Ship, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Personal- Tolly Pickett, Ocracoke, Skiing, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Personal- Chrome Leica III, Summar, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Personal- Sal, Trip, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 4-5)
      - United Way- Awards Meeting, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 6-7)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 8-10)
      - Personal- IIIA & late Summar- ( House in Canon 1.8), 1984 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Camera Test, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - 1984 Roller Rides- Monroeville Mall (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 14, 22, 51)
      - Personal- IIIC, w/ Summintar Test, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center- Awards Breakfast- Jack Lambert and Ken Mease, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 16-17)
      - Personal- ACA Roller Races, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 18-19)
      - Personal- Coll 'cron & 2.8 Sereuar Test, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Bio-Energetics, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - P.A. B., 1984 (Box 60, Folder 23-26)
      - United Way- Labor Meeting, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 27-29)
      - Personal- Ocracoke Easter 1984 (Box 60, Folder 30)
      - Personal- IIIA, 3.5 Elmar, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - Nancy William- Head Shots for Passports, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - Golden Quill Awards, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 33-34)
      - Test on OM-1, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - IIIa Elmar, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - III F Red Dial Test, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - United Way- Market Square, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 38-42)
      - Personal- III F, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 43)
      - Personal- III F RD, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 44)
      - United Way- Lucius Middlebrook- Wilkinsburg H.S., 1984 (Box 60, Folder 45)
      - Fotomat, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 46)
      - United Way Posters- Anna Fireman at Vintage, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 47)
      - United Way Posters- Anna Fireman, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 48)
      - United Way- Richard Gray- Stroke, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 49)
      - United Way- Richard Gray – Stroke Victim, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 50)
      - United Way- Salvation Army- Food District, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 52)
      - Know Kekew- Copy of old family picture, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 53)
      - United Way- Labor Meeting, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 54)
      - United Way- Labor Meeting- Press Club, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 55)
      - United Way- Lau(d)ed(?) Execs, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
      - Hot Harry's, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - United Way- PPG Plaza R, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 4-8)
      - United Way- Pacesetter Report Lunch, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
      - Bio-Energetics, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 11-13)
      - Eye Bank, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 14-15)
      - United Way- Meadows Meeting, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 16-19)
      - Personal- Misc. M4-2, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - United Way- William Penn, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 21-24)
      - Personal- 100mm Zuiko fz test, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation- Details, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - Personal- IIIf, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - Sweetwater- Textile Details, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 28)
      - Copper & Brass Sales Inc., 1984 (Box 61, Folder 29)
      - Personal- Canon 1.2 Tests, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 30)
      - M4-2 w/ Canon 1.2, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 31)
      - Contax IIA w/ 2.8, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 32)
      - M4-2, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 33)
      - Personal- IIIA Summitar, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 34)
      - Sweetwater- Wing Ding Promo, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 35, 37-38)
      - Personal- Summitar Test, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 36)
      - Summilux – Canon Test, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 39)
      - Personal- IIIb w/ ctd Summitar Test, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 40)
      - Personal- Camera Tests, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - 1985
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment; Gatan Inc.; United Way; Oracoke Island, North Carolina; Pittsburgh Blind Association; Golden Quill Awards; Pittsburgh Blind Association; Bike Race; Hot Harry's Picnic; Bio-Energetiks. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Contax 1.5 at Ocracoke, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 42)
      - Personal- Christmas 1984- Ocracoke, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 43-45)
      - Ocracoke Sunset, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 46)
      - United Way- Annual Meeting – William Penn, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 47-50)
      - Personal- House in snow at night- Christmas cards?, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Personal- Snow Scenes- Winter Wonderland Workshop, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Personal- IIIF Pair Pictures, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Bio-Energetics- Bearer Office, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 4-5)
      - Personal- Cross Country Skiing w/ Bashfords, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Personal- Color – M-2, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 8-10, 51-56)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Cranberry, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Personal- Leica III, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Personal- Canon w/ 1.2 Canon, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Personal- Copy work for Anne Jenkins Bradford Woods Book, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - III Chrome, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Personal- M-2, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Ann Jenkins- Copies of old photos – Bradford Woods, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - United Way- Labor Meeting at Press Club, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 18-19)
      - Personal- D.C. Trip, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 20)
      - Aerial Views- Bradford Woods, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - Ocracoke '85 Easter & Aerial Views of Bradford Woods, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 22)
      - Dynamic Equipment- Copy of Cutout, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 23)
      - United Way- Holy Family/Hill House, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 24)
      - United Way- Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 25-26)
      - United Way- Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 27, 32, 38, 41, 44-45)